He's a dreamer, stuck in the real world.
Griff the Invisible is a romance, comedy, drama film directed by Leon Ford.
Griff, office worker by day, superhero by night, has his world turned upside down when he meets
Melody, a beautiful young scientist who shares his passion for the impossible.
Griff, played by Ryan Kwanten.
Melody, played by Maeve Dermody.
Tim, played by Patrick Brammall.
Tony, played by Toby Schmitz.
Benson, played by Marshall Napier.
Bronwyn, played by Heather Mitchell.
Griff the Invisible is a 2010 Australian romantic superhero
comedy-drama film written and directed by Leon Ford.
Its storyline centres on a socially awkward office worker bullied by his workmates during the daytime and turning
himself at nighttime into a superhero who roams the streets of his neighbourhood and protects the innocent.
Griff the Invisible had its world premiere at the 2010 Toronto International Film Festival (TIFF),
where it was well received by audiences "who seemed charmed by this offbeat tale".
It also screened at the 2011 Berlin International Film Festival in February 2011 in the
"generation" sidebar where it was well received by a predominantly teenage crowd.
The film won the AACTA award for Best Original Screenplay.
The film explores themes of superhero, bullying, love, loneliness, scientist.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.